curbly.com 2018-10-12

# 

## Curbly LLC Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This policy explains our information practices, defines your privacy options and describes how your information is collected and used by us, Curbly, LLC ("Curbly").

This policy covers the website at http://www.curbly.com (the "Curbly Website").

By using visiting the Curbly Website, you agree to the collection and use of information in the manner described in this policy. Curbly shall have right at any time and without prior notice, at its sole discretion, to revise this policy. Such revisions and additions shall be effective immediately upon notice, which may be given by any means, including but not limited to posting the revised or additional terms and conditions on the Curbly Website. You are responsible for reviewing the Curbly Website periodically for any modification to this policy. 

### The Information We Collect 

This policy applies to all information collected on the Curbly Website and any information you provide to Curbly. You will most likely provide us personal information to us when you register as a Curbly Website user, participate in certain Curbly promotions or enter certain Curbly sponsored contests. The personal information we may collect includes:

  * User ID
  * Password
  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number 

Our advertising partners may engage in the collection of non-personally identifiable information about you through the use of cookies and pixel tags.

You can opt out of behavioral targeting through the opt-out link located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We are participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising, with the provision an "Ad Choices" link on our site or within advertising units that link to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. 

The information you submit to Curbly may also include text, photographs, video, graphics, music and any other materials you might submit as part of, or in conjunction with, your use of the Curbly Website. 

### Our Collection of Your Data

In addition to the personal information you supply, we collect certain information to evaluate how visitors, guests, and members use the Curbly Website. We collect data to make our service work better for you in the following ways: to improve the design of the Curbly Website, to provide personalization on the Curbly Website, and to evaluate the performance of our marketing programs. The technologies we use to gather this non-personal information may include IP addresses, cookies, clear gifs, and browser detection.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Advertising and Privacy â€“ Google Privacy Center").

### Affiliate Link Disclosure

Curbly participates in an affiliate program with Amazon.com and SkimLinks.com. Links originating on Curbly sites that lead to product purchases through these vendors generate affiliate revenue for Curbly. 

Learn more about SkimLinks affiliate links here: <http://skimlinks.com/privacy#visit>. You can disable the use of Skimlinks optimisation cookies. Visit this link to learn how: <http://skimlinks.com/privacy#personalizedlinks>. 

### Sponsored Posts

Curbly may accept and publish sponsored posts, which will be highlighted as sponsored content. While we may be compensated for creating this content, all opinions contained therein are ours alone.

### Chatrooms, bulletin boards and product reviews 

The Curbly Website may include chatrooms, bulletin boards, product reviews, or other message areas that allow users to post information to the Curbly Website. When you post messages, other site visitors can also view them. We urge you to exercise caution when providing personally identifiable financial or other information in the chatrooms, bulletin boards, product reviews or other message areas. Remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information. 

### How we use information 

Our primary goal in collecting your customer information is to provide you with a personalized, relevant, and positive experience with the Curbly Website. Curbly will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to others except as set forth in this policy. 

You can register on the Curbly Website to receive promotions and updates, or to be contacted for market research purposes. The contact information you submit will not be used for these purposes unless you specifically "opt-in". You can control your privacy preferences regarding such marketing communications (see the section below entitled "Your Privacy Preferences"). 

From time to time, you may be invited to participate in optional customer surveys or contests, and Curbly may request that you provide some or all of the above listed personal information in those surveys or contests. We use information collected through contests to contact winners and award prizes. We use information collected from surveys to learn about our customers in order to improve our services and develop new products and services of interest to our customers. 

Curbly uses IP addresses, cookies, clear gifs, browser detection, and weblogs to provide a better experience on our website and to give us useful business information. 

IP addresses define the Internet location of computers and help us better understand the geographic distribution of our members and manage the performance of the Curbly Website. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you visit the Curbly Website, so we can immediately recognize you when you return to the site and deliver content specific to your interests. You may modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. Please consult your browser instructions for information on how to modify your choices about cookies. 

We also use a technology called clear gifs. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with unique identifiers that are used to track emails and online movements, helping us understand what marketing campaigns and content are effective. 

We detect the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of our website and to understand the mix of browsers used by our visitors, guests, and members. To learn about how people use our site, we examine weblogs, which show the paths people take through our site and how long they spend in certain areas. 

Curbly also sometimes contract with unaffiliated third parties to provide services, such as software for site features, customer communications, sweepstakes and prize fulfillment, analyzing and evaluating the information we collect, and other services. When we do this, we may provide your personally identifiable information to third parties only to provide those services, and they are not authorized to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

###  Our Commitment to Data Security 

Access to your data is limited to authorized Curbly staff or approved vendors. Although total security does not exist on the Internet, Curbly shall make commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the information that you submit to Curbly. 

###  Use of the Curbly Website by Children 

The products and services offered by Curbly are not intended for use by children. Curbly will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information submitted by visitors to the Curbly Website site who are under the age of 13. 

###  Your Privacy Preferences 

When you sign up as a registered Curbly user, you may begin receiving marketing communications such as e-mail newsletters, product and service updates, promotions, and contests. Our customers generally find this type of information useful. If you do not want to receive these updates, you must "opt-out" by unchecking the "I would like receive occasional updates from the Curbly Team." box on the registration page, or should you choose to opt-out after registering, you can use any of the following three methods: select the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email and follow the opt-out instructions; go to your user page, select "Edit Account", then select and de-select the appropriate box; or send an email to support@curbly.com. 

###  How to Access or Correct Your Information 

You can access and maintain your personally identifiable information on your User profile page. To protect your privacy and security, we require a user ID and password to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

###  Legal Disclaimers

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. It is also possible that Curbly would sell all or substantially all of its assets and business. In any transaction of this kind, customer information, including your personally identifiable information, may be among the assets that are transferred. If we decide to so transfer your personally identifiable information, you will be notified by email. 

The Curbly Website may contain links to other websites. Curbly is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each web site that collects personally identifiable information. Some linked sites may be co-branded with our trademarks and those of our business partners. They may have the look and feel of www.curbly.com, but the URL in your browser window will indicate that you are visiting a different site. This policy only applies to information collected by Curbly. 

###  How to Contact Us 

Should you have privacy questions or concerns, send an email to support@curbly.com.
